hey what's up everybody Jeremiah Kowski
here listen I'm going to show you how to
create custom AI agents that can do
amazing things for your business so you
don't have to waste time struggling to
make things work and it can actually
save you a lot of time and effort to get
the results that you're looking for out
of using artificial intelligence by the
end of this video I'm going to be
showing you a method that actually I've
never taught publicly to anybody and I
probably actually haven't taught it in
depth to even my high level coaching
group but I use it behind the scenes and
you're going to get this from me just
from this video okay so for those of you
that I have not met yet my name is
Jeremiah Kowski for the last 21 years I
have been building coaching course and
training businesses I built multiple
businesses over the $10 million year
mark in this space of coaching and
courses and training and I show people
how to use advertising and marketing and
and I love using AI not as something
that replaces us in our marketing but
helps us brainstorm ideas and so that's
what I'm going to be showing you how to
do is how to actually create custom GP
pts CU you don't have to buy all these
prompt packs and all this you can
actually have the AI in chat GPT do a
lot of the work for you okay so I'm
excited to actually share this with you
and walk you through this process okay
so first off what I want to tell you is
what a custom GPT is basically a custom
GPT is a it's this thing inside a chat
GPT and you and you have to you have to
pay for chat GPT to be able to create
gpts but they recently released and it's
amazing you can actually use gpts
without having to pay for them so you if
you have a free account with ch GPT you
can go to open.com and get a free
account with chat GPT highly recommend
it uh I mean like you you're doing
yourself a disservice if you don't okay
you go to products and go to um chat GPT
and you can create an account okay and
so then you can click on explore gpts
you got to log in and actually create a
account to be able to find these um once
you do this look there's so many
different categories that you can search
for to find things that do different
stuff inside of chat GPT for you such
incredible things like this one right
here is so cool AI humanizer it can take
what the AI generates and then help
humanize it there's a copywriter GPT for
ads and
copywriting um and there and the list
goes on as far as that goes and what is
a GPT so to answer that question
basically a GPT is a custom version of
chat GPT with extra instructions and
sometimes extra knowledge that can do
amazing skills that just out of the box
it doesn't do and you can actually
search for gpts right here like I could
search for uh Facebook
ads and so I could actually find custom
gpts that people have
created uh to do things with Facebook
ads Facebook ads virtual assistant talk
with your ads data Facebook ads
copyright wror uh meta ads copy Wizard
and so listen it's so cool that we can
actually access these to be able to do
this if I put uh uh landing page sales
copy right if I type that in landing
page sales copy writer uh right here now
here's what I want to show you how to do
is how to actually create your own
custom gpts first off I'm going to show
you the difference between this let's
say that we we go to the Facebook ads
one right here and I'm going to show you
the difference that this makes using
something like one of these Facebook ads
copywriters versus just doing it on your
own you can even see ratings that people
have rid the GPT which is also really
really cool this one's decent if it's
above a four star rating I think that's
pretty pretty good uh they have a start
button here so let's check out what this
is please upload your your completed
brand in the Box text file okay well
we're not going to do that so we're
going
to do a new chat right there so we do
this okay watch
write me a Facebook ad to promote an
online coaching business that gets more
leads for people who become clients
okay I'll create three different ad
sets uh unlock your full potential in
coaching 50% off your first session are
you ready to take your business Next
Level our expert online coaching
services are designed to help you
generate more leads okay so it gives you
ideas for like what to create with ads
copy now that's cool but that's based on
somebody's opinion of what it is what I
love and if you follow me for any length
of time is I love to teach you how to
take more control of what you're doing
so that it works a lot better okay so if
we go to explore gbts and we click on
create I can actually go here and I can
click this under create and it says hey
there I will help you build a GPT okay
make a creative that generates visuals
okay I want you you to study all the
best
copywriters like Sandy Kowski and Dan
Kennedy and
Russell
Brunson and create the best Facebook ads
using the
Pas framework so this combines a few
things that I'm telling it right here
and let me actually move my my my face
to this upper corner
here so you can kind of see a little bit
better I'm going to shrink my face down
too just a little bit there we go okay
I'm in the top corner there now instead
of the instead of that that part of the
frame so you should be able to see more
of it if I do that what's up everybody
okay so I'm going to tell it this it's
like what would you like me to make I'm
going to tell it to do this and now it's
going to go to work and process there's
this magic that sort of happens behind
the scenes where it's going to take what
I just told it I told it to make it like
the best copywriters to use the Pas
framework and to make the best Facebook
ads so it goes to work and it generates
all these different ideas for what that
might look
like to create a custom GPT
okay and now I can save it would you
like to call it add copy Master
sure
okay and so now it's able to create
these compelling Facebook ads based on
this next I'll generate a profile
picture so it's generating an image now
for the for the um GPT
and there's something really really cool
that we can do as well okay here's the
initial profile for ad copy Master do
you like it sure that's
fine and and it's always going to ask
you what you want the name to be and
what you want the image to be okay what
what should be emphasized or avoided
when creating the Facebook ads well
these ads are made to attract more
clients
with their two our lead magnet to get
people to sign up for our webinar so I'm
giving it some context I didn't actually
answer its question exactly as it gave
and you might notice maybe you get
confused you're like oh well I don't
know how to answer its questions I don't
know what that that is just tell it more
of what you want it to do as far as that
goes which is the tone be uh I do know
this persuasive informal and
conversation
in the tone of Russell Brunson Sandy
Kowski and Dan Kennedy which anytime we
do anything with copyrighting those
those tone of voices always work really
well especially if I use like all three
of them as far as that goes
okay it's going to kind of bring all of
that together to help us write these
really really good uh forms of Facebook
ad copy
okay and I'm actually going to give you
a link to this GPT in the in the
description below there anything
specific you want to ensure to include
or avoid um don't overuse
emojis too much a little bit is
okay and make sure to act as an expert
in writing ads and sales copy that gets
people's
attention specifically with the first
line
of copy so for me I know that that's
what the copy should have in it and so
I'm able to feed into the GPT to
actually create a custom version of chat
GPT based on the type of output that I
want it to create okay now behind the
scenes what it's
creating is it's creating a set of
custom instructions and we can go in and
we can refine this even more but if we
go under configure this is what it's
really
creating is this block right here this
block of text right here is what the AI
is generating and it tells it what to do
this GPT is an expert at crafting High
conversion Facebook ads using the
problem agitate solution framework ASP
of by top copywriter Sandy Kowski Dan
Kenny and Russell Brunson it excels at
identifying Target customer pain points
agitating those to heighten urgency and
presenting compelling Solutions the goal
is to help them create help users create
engaging Facebook ads that resonate With
Their audience boost conversions to
attract clients to their lead magnets
and encourage webinar
signups and I might change that to to to
say um webinar signups or
signups to whatever offer They are
promoting as long as people need to
register with their information or
purchase something it will provide
clear concise and persuasive copy
and actually we're going to go it'll
provide in a
persuasive
informal and conversational
tone okay best copy is going to be
informal conversational and
persuasive uh oh wait it already says
that there so we can remove that
perfect so if I remove that that section
right there about it being
persuasive uh conversational all that
okay we're going to go back here uh
ensuring the ads are tailored to the
user specific needs and objectives it
avoids overly complex language focusing
instead on strong emotional appeal and
direct call to action the ads will be
persuasive informative and
conversational no not informative they
need to be in
formal
informal
informal meaning it's not
formal
okay uh reflecting the tone of C Kowski
Ross Bruns and Dan Kennedy to avoid
overuse of emojis incorporating them
sparingly we focus on capturing the
attention with strong impactful first
line of copy gbt acts as an expert in
writing ads and sales copy that grabs
attention Okay so right there the AI
gener ated a prompt for us and and you
have to pay for chat gbt plus to be able
to get this feature but this can save
you so much time if you're like I just
can't seem to get the AI to tell to give
me what I want I can't seem to get it to
do what I want it to do
okay I can save this I can even put this
into um the GPT store right here add
copy Master okay
there we go okay now so if we view the
GPT uh here's the
offer I'm promoting okay let's say that
I go take an offer right here um here's
an offer that we worked on with a client
for a wellness
webinar okay we're going to take this
copy from their
page minus the bonuses and we're going
to tell it to create ads based on this
right here tired of feeling like your
body is running slow Take Back Control
ladies it's time to turn back the clock
take a charge of your
health awesome
highlights perfect so um one thing that
I wanted to do is I wanted to generate
me couple versions of that so that so
here's now what you want to what you
want to do this is not outputting how we
want it to so I'm going to now go
and correct it just a little bit
we're going to go over here edit GPT
okay um this this isn't generating ads
the best way and they
aren't good ads uh can
you make four
versions for each
ad and make them
them closely follow
the Pas
framework for ad
copy
okay I know I misspelled a few there
let's refine this okay add
copy general theme that illustrates what
that's like yep exactly
specific topics you want to use whatever
the users input please update the GP
okay
so now it's going in and it's updating
the GPT based on what I corrected it
with so we're now we're going to take
this copy right here and we're going to
test it again
okay all
right perfect
into some
ads there we go ad number
one are you exhausted let's see feeling
like your body is in control instead of
you I was there too join me for the yeah
so this is great so this is like a great
format for writing copy as far as that
goes um can you have the GPT expand the
opening copy just a bit
more to agitate the pain points in the
format and be less informative and
more direct okay so again this is just
creating a GPT that does add copy right
here I'm going to show you a few other
ways of doing this but this is how I
would refine an advertising GPT as far
as that goes okay I'm going to show you
another version of creating a GPT one
that can actually work really well for
your mental health as well that's also
really really cool
okay so if we update
this I'm going view the
GPT write some ads
based okay there's our
offer here's our ads and yes it's
finally it's starting to hit exactly
what I'm looking for so this is great so
we' we' refined it to really help us
write good ads and we can use this now
every time we want to write ads all I
got to do is just open up this ad copy
Master right here and actually use it
now I have created some mindful uh guide
virtual therapist ones right here and
you can see what these gpts are as well
this one right here act as a virtual
therapist trained in cognitive
behavioral therapy and internal family
systems provides guidance and grading
fractured parts of one's personality
diving into root cause issues in a
non-intrusive safe manner GPT encourages
open discussion about difficult
repressed memories offering supportive
and thoughtful responses to facilitate
self-awareness so how did I create this
let's just say we want to create
one that's that's kind of like
this
okay we can go to the GPT explore
GPT and we can say
I want a GPT to help me process my
mental health and
anxiety
issues uh it's trained
in
CBT
and ifs
therapy and works to
integrate different parts of okay
great so it's going to go to work and
actually start to create something that
even you could use for your mental
health out of the box it's not going to
be the best at that's mindful support
sure like mindful guide but we're
calling it mindful support okay let's
create a profile picture for it first
version let me
know if you'd like any changes now
there's not like one best way to create
a GPT or to to use the GPT Builder
there's a lot of different things that
you can do with the GPT Builder
uh to put stuff out there and to reach
people that's very interesting that
photo uh sure that's
good we'll use this photo right
here okay let me assist any aspect
emphasize or avoided um I'd like it
to always ask questions to dig deeper
and get to the root cause so it's
effective at actual behavioral
and habit change okay cuz that's what
we're looking for we're looking for
something that can actually help us
change our behavior and identify what
those root causes
are and so this is a great way to be
able to do this and have something that
you could talk with specific techniques
or approaches um I'd like it to help
script out and
identify different parts and facil
facilitate
conversation
internally with those as well as ask
questions to help May
truly resolve these issues it should act
as an expert in these
modalities of therapy
okay there we go and so that's what you
can do is you can talk with the GPT
Builder and have it start to build out
number of different um ways of doing
things how would you like to communicate
with you um more
personal
go more
personal and so as you can see it can
take some time to be able to do this you
can try it out here's what it generated
off of that again very similar to what
we put in there um it avoids giving
medical advice or making diagnosis
focusing on instead of facilitating
self-discovery so I'm actually going to
remove that
line they have to put that in there for
safety quote unquote for to cover their
butt but I I would remove that
personally uh from
it because then it can actually be a
little bit more effective as far as that
goes all right
cool create
save let's go take a look at
it and see how well it does all
right I'm struggling with staying
focused when I get triggered by
someone criticizing me on the the
internet saying I'm stupid in the
comments of my YouTube
videos
okay sounds like receiving negative
comments is really impacting your focus
first you can describe how you feel when
you read those comments so look it's
starting to ask questions can you
describe how you feel when you read
those comments what particular thoughts
come to
mind and you might notice it can start
to overwhelm you with a lot of questions
so we might go back and I might actually
optimize this and say um
um this is good the questions asked are
good but it can get
overwhelming with too many questions can
you have it never ask more
than
one question at a time that is well
thought
out and asks followup and continued
questions after each
answer is given to create a more natural
experience okay so it's going to only
ask one question at a time instead of
overwhelming you with a ton of questions
that's one of the things that I noticed
that my you know my older version of
this kind of did it
was all right let's update it and let's
take a look at it
there we
go all right um I experien a lot of
anxiety when people uh judge me harshly
on the internet for my videos I make on
YouTube and it shuts down my creativity
for weeks at a time sometimes all
right sounds really challenging when you
read these harsh judgments or feelings
what does do they bring up Are there
specific phrases that impact you the
most uh people saying that I'm
stupid
uninformed don't know what I'm talking
about or should just give up shut up or
go to jail for what I say okay so like
we're just going to give like an example
of that this sounds incredibly hurtful
it can be really challenging let's
unpack this a bit when you read these
you know specific thoughts go through
your mind about yourself yeah I feel
like
if only I could be more perfect then
things wouldn't feel so
hurtful it's understandable you feel
that way especially I'm facing harsh
criticism when you think about being
more perfect what does that look like to
so you can see how valuable this could
be to really start to identify these
things for you as far as that goes and
I've created a number of different gpts
I have one right here called book
insights Guru um
you know I'm I'm
enjoying reading uh The
Circle
Series by Ted Decker what are other
series that I may enjoy it can give me
ideas as far as that goes because it's
an expert on different um series of of
things that's interesting because I
actually thought a lot about these
and The Mortal Instrument sounds pretty
interesting too the lightbringer series
The Wheel of Time yeah honestly like
this totally makes sense though um as
far as the narrative style of this
series Falls in alignment with a lot of
those okay uh belief changer this one's
interesting I had this create a GPT this
one's very interesting because it's
about helping you re-evaluate and modify
your beliefs so I went in and I told it
I want you to be able to take a belief
and unpack pack it in a way that helps
people adjust what they believe it's to
facilitate shifting of belief and
transition to create a script of that
okay struggling and believing I'm worthy
of Love
okay acknowledge your feelings I
recognize that right now identify the
root cause of it challenge the current
belief look for contradictions remember
times with my friend showed me love
introduce A New
Perspective so the custom gpts are
designed to do what they say they're
going to do you know here's one I
created with a client right here sleep
Wellness guide they were in the Sleep
Wellness space and so he said okay let's
go create a wellness guide that somebody
can use this one's called RPG in a
GPT and so the idea is um let's begin
it'll literally start to create uh a
video game World anytime you want you
can go into it welcome to meor your
Journey Begins in your backpack you have
a small dagger or water
flask uh number two okay so it's like a
Choose Your Own Adventure type mission
that the AI is actually generating as
far as this
goes ask Luna about the pendant on her
neck okay
and you know it's interesting this this
GPT was supposed
to also
create um images anytime it it did
something but doesn't seem like it it's
an older one I had
created and so it would be interesting
it it kind of like creates a game that
you can explore and stuff like that
okay uh flow speed typist this one was
interesting this one is where like I can
I can type like this like I want to know
if you can see exactly what I'm typing
I'm just going really fast and you can
edit this and make this much better okay
so obviously that's terrible as far as
what that is
but look at that the GPT can literally
go to work and and fix what I was typing
so you could like get into the flow and
type really fast so you would create a
GPT that can do
that by giving it the type of behavior
that you want it to do and then telling
it how you want it to act and behave
okay and you can use these to then do
different things in your life here's one
called podcast Creator I actually
created this one um if I can take a
transcript for a podcast it'll generate
titles descriptions Instagram posts and
and uh All That B just based on a
recorded
podcast um recording let's say I want to
create one for YouTube videos like
this there's a practical one right here
I could go create a GPT that
says I want to paste a transcript of a
YouTube
video in and generate 20 possible titles
and description for the
YouTube video okay and so it can go to
work to start to create some of these as
far as that
goes as a GPT that it can create okay
that's interesting it showed us
uh what it was actually going to work to
do
something went wrong uh yes that's
good it's having a little bit of trouble
with the GPT right there but you get the
idea for like how you create gpts now
here's another cool thing that you can
do is you don't have to just use chat
GPT to do do this type of stuff you can
go in and find the The Prompt that it
generates where it says instructions
right
here this is the custom prompt that it's
generating you can copy that and if you
go into a tool called po.com which has a
number of different AI algorithms you
can create a
bot that does different things based on
instructions that you give it okay so
for instance if I want to
select
um Claude 3.5 Sonet and then give it
this same prompt from the custom GPT you
can also upload a knowledge Source if
you have transcripts you can do this in
the GPT editor you can
upload files of
transcripts of knowledge that you have
either about what you want it to do how
you want it to act how you want it to
react and it can pull from that as well
as far as that goes
so this might
be a mindful ifs
CBT there
CBT
mindful ifs CBT bot
okay there we go so what I was able to
do now is I was able to take that prompt
hey there I'm
struggling with feeling
anxious and people are really negative
towards me on social
media okay and so it's going to use
different AI algorithms like Claude 3 to
be able to do that sorry to hear you're
struggling it's common issue people face
can you tell me a bit more about the
specific
situation where you feel anxious um I
posted a video Someone CR critic
ized me for being too
overweight in the video okay which
that's actually happened to me before uh
negative experiences how do you feel in
the moment we first saw well I was mad I
also thought they
were they were dumb and I didn't want to
get into
it with them okay so what I'm trying to
show you here is that you can create
these different avatars and personas and
different things with AI where it can
act and respond in a very specific
way not just how it is out of the box
and then that can give you much higher
quality information if you use something
like Po you can play around with
different algorithms to be able to do
different things like that like if I
want to edit this bot right here I can
have it use a different AI algorithm
like
Gemini and see what kind of outputs it
gives me based on Gemini for the same
question okay let's go
explore my bot right here there we
go type this in but it's going to use
Gemini now to answer this hey there
sounds like you're having a tough times
understand you feel anxious tell me more
about what specifically makes you
anxious in those
situations I don't like when people say
these mean
things can you give me an example of a
comment that that that you receive yeah
so it's going to it's going to work
differently depending on uh which AI you
use uh using po but
overall these are great tools that you
can use to be able to have the AI
operate in different ways custom ways uh
to to produce some different results as
far as it goes here's one other thing
that I like to do let's say I was trying
to like brainstorm different ideas this
is something I was doing on one of my
coaching calls right here and we typed
in a bunch of transcripts and stuff like
that on it let's say that I want to tell
it generate me instructions to give to
an AI bot that is an expert in the above
and
create these instructions to create an
AI agent that can do the above as an
expert okay instructions for bot for
creating lead magnet for customer
acquisition goal you're an AI expert at
crafting this common
problems recommended two three lead
magnet ideas generate compelling sales
copy so the AI is now giving me ideas
for how a bot would work as far as that
goes and I might be able to either copy
this as the custom instruction
or now I've never done this before but
we're going to try something
or we can go right over to chat
GPT and I'll tell you what's the
difference between doing doing that and
doing it with po the GPT Builder and the
way that it works is just it's a little
bit better in in just it's like overall
quality and ease of use but if I paste
that prompt that I generated over there
it's going to give me the initial
behavior of what I want it to do for
me
um inside of this as far as that goes uh
sure sales copy
Maestro let's create a profile picture
and I would maybe wait till after it
finishes this
step
um and I might paste the exact same
context that we generated into it to
help it update the GPT to create this
kind
of response or
prompt what does it do how does it
behave
I'm just going to I'm going to paste my
same prompt in there let's refine it
further could you provide more details
as far as the
approach different
Industries Okay so so now it created
this right here this gpts to assist in
creating compelling sales copy messaging
for their ideas it'll CFT attention
grabbing headlines let's speak directly
to the audience's paino write persuasive
body copy that expands the so you can
see how it's able to do
that let's go in and try this one out
right
here and these are different ways that I
love to use AI to really optimize and
customize what the output is as far as
this goes okay um can you make
me make me some ideas around painfree
birth it's just one idea that I know
some people
have here's some headline
ideas body copy ideas honestly like this
is great as far as the GPT goes this is
super
cool and so this can help you get even
better at creating copy creating your
offer creating The Language by using AI
to give you some of these ideas and
using custom gpts for this so listen go
ahead play around with those different
custom gpts this is something that I
that I encourage all of my students to
do inside of my coaching program the
accelerator program this is something
that I Mentor them on is using AI as far
as this goes listen if you are a coach
Mentor or trainer and you want to get
more clients in your business I'd love
to work with you in my accelerator
program where I can take a look at your
offers and your copy and see okay how
are we using this over here is this
working together the right way are those
pieces fitting together well to be able
to help you refine your your your
messaging dial in your Niche start to
generate more leads in your business so
then you can start to close more sales
for you it's exactly what I help people
with every single day and so you can
join my accelerator program you'll find
the link below as well for that and I'd
love to work with you in that we'll talk
soon everybody have a good one